A Guide to the Memorabilia FA437
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Laurance S. Rockefeller, 5
  - honorary resolution from Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Oversized (Object 4022)
  - memorial for Carlisle Humelsine, from Jackson Hole Pr., 1989 September 27; bound in blue clamshell (Object 4023)
  - Pierre Award, Westchester County Parks & Recreation, 1967 May 22 (Object 4024)
  - miniature elephant "from Thai Ambassador" (Object 4025, Box 3)
  - Erlacher Glass paperweight, from Cornell School of Hotel Administration, 1989 April 1; in red velvet box (Object 4026, Box 3)
  - plaque from YMCA of Puerto Rico, 1964 (Object 4027, Box 4)
  - membership, Chancellor's Council, University of Texas, 1983 October 1 (Object 4028)
  - small signed portrait, Charles F. Kettering, pair w/ # 4030 (Object 4029)
  - small signed portrait, Alfred P. Sloan, pair w/ #4029 (Object 4030)
  - plaque & award, from William P. Mott Memorial Fund, 1997 May 10; documents stored separately (Object 4031)
  - medal, Medical University Faculty in Sao Paolo, 1994 (Object 4032, Box 3)
  - membership, Palmer C. Ricketts Society, Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1989-1990 (Object 4033)
  - Woodrow Wilson Award, from Princeton University, 1991 February 16; 2 plaques (Object 4034)
  - Francis Peltier,pres. of Virgin Islands State Park, w/child, 1997 (Object 4035)
  - color print of Billings Farm & Museum, Woodstock VT, 1993 (Object 4036)
  - honorary degree, California Institute of Integral Studies, 1998 June 27 (Object 4037, Box 4)
  - plaque, Alexis de Tocqueville Society/ United Way, 1998; see #5054 (Object 4038)
  - photo of MIT Corporation in President's Garden, 1997 September 26 (Object 4039)
  - plaque from NYC World's Fair, sent to Mary French from "JPL", 1964 (Object 4040, Box 3)
  - James Ewing Award, Society of Surgical Oncology, 1981 (Object 4041, Box 5)
  - plaque, America's Future Trees (Chairman of 2 committees), 1957-1965 (Object 4042)
  - commission to Republican Inner Circle, w/ letter, to Mary F., 1991 (Object 4043)
  - Lelooska tribe carving (small totem pole) w/ 2 wings in appreciation from Natll Park Foundation, 1978 April 7; inscribed plaque on one wing; 3 separately wrapped packages (Object 4044)
  - birthday card from staff of RockResorts, 1980 May (Object 4045, Box 5)
  - certificate from Parkinson's Action Network, w/ letter, 1997 April 29 (Object 4046, Box 5)
  - illuminated quotation by William Beebe, from Bronx Zoo (Object 4047)
  - acrylic paperweight w/ green maple leaf icon (Object 4048)
  - framed prayer of St. Francis, matches NAR #934 (Object 4049)
  - glass paperweight from WETA campaign, 1999 May 1 (Object 4050, Box 3)
  - Hawaii Salesman of the Year, 1966 (Object 4051)
  - bronze card holder, from Outdoor Recreational Review Commission from Henry L. Diamond (Object 4052, Box 3)
  - brass clock, in thanks for work at Mauna Kea Beach Hawaii, 1960-1980 (Object 4053, Box 3)
  - silver case w/ calendar from Weill Cornell Medical College, 1990-1999 (Object 4054, Box 3)
  - crystal brick, Century Society's 2nd Century campaign, 1998 (Object 4055, Box 3)
  - pencil holder, Wood's Hole Oceanographic Institution (Object 4056, Box 3)
  - large plaque from Golden Anniversary of NYC, 1948 (Object 4057, Box 1)
  - certificate of membership, Flying Fisherman Club, 1955 March 5 (Object 4058, Box 1)
  - plaque, St. Thomas Chamber of Commerce, Virgin Islands, 1966 July 1 (Object 4059, Box 1)
  - plaque, New England Outdoor Writers' Assoc., 1964 January 1 (Object 4060, Box 1)
  - plaque, Virgin Gorda B.V.I., 1972 May 6 (Object 4061, Box 1)
  - plaque, U.S.S. Saratoga (Object 4062, Box 1)
  - plaque, Midwest Travel Writers Assoc. Award, 1964 (Object 4063, Box 1)
  - public recreation award, from Secretary Udall, Dept of the Interior, 1962 May 25 (Object 4064, Box 1)
  - "Freedom of the Human Spirit" award given to LSR "With Dedication Always MMB" (Object 4065)
- David Rockefeller, 6
  - bronze bust of D. D. Eisenhower, from West Point, 1982 April 1 (Object 5000, Box 7)
  - 5 prints of DR w/ Mayor LaGuardia, from George Weissman, 1940 (Object 5001)
    w/ note from Room 5600
  - 5 pictures of DR in Chase Manhattan folders (Object 5002)
  - MacDowell Colony Award disc and crystal block, 1982; in 2 gray boxes in paige box (Object 5003, Box 7)
  - mounted medal for establishing Ramon Magsaysay Award, 1950 August 31 (Object 5004)
  - 2 copies of speech about DR by pres. of Middlebury College, 1974 May 26; in white envelope in paige box (Object 5005, Box 2)
  - Hilal-i-Quaid-i-Azam award, Pakistan, with letters, 1984 August 30; in green box "Mr. Arnaud de Borchgrave" (Object 5006, Box 6)
  - medal: Orden de Vasco Nunez de Balboa, 1961; note: received in Panama (Object 5007, Box 6)
  - silver plate, merger of Outlet Company & Rockefeller Center, 1984 January 31; in small red box (Object 5008, Box 1)
  - commemorative gold coin from Pope's visit, 1986 March 19 (Object 5009, Box 1)
  - gold, silver, diamond pin of sword in a stone (Object 5010, Box 1)
  - commemorative gold coin from U. of Paris 50th anniversary, 1987 (Object 5011, Box 1)
    w/note
  - set of coins from Central Bank of Ireland (Object 5012, Box 1)
  - 6 commemorative coins from 22nd Olympics-Moscow, 1980 (Object 5013, Box 1)
  - 6 commemorative coins from USSR (Object 5014, Box 1)
  - commemorative coin by Vasco Berardo, Portugal, 1973; Christmas gift, w/note (Object 5015, Box 1)
  - medal from Senegal (Object 5016, Box 1)
  - medal from Cameroun, 1961 (Object 5017, Box 1)
  - Legion d'Honneur-rank of Commander medal, 1975 February 28; w/ speech stored seperately (Object 5018, Box 1)
  - Legion d'Honneur-rank of Commander medal - speech, 1975 February 28; Medal stored separately. (Object 5018, Box 2)
  - plaque & historic stamp, for 100th anniv. of Statue of Liberty, 1986 December 4 (Object 5019, Box 1)
  - paperweight w/coin, from Banco Nacional de Cuba, 1958; wrapped seperately in same box (Object 5020, Box 1)
  - bronze medal from Christian Democratic Party in Italy, 1971 (Object 5021, Box 1)
    from "Mr. Dimita"
  - Bank of Israel medal-20th anniversary, 1974 (Object 5022, Box 1)
  - 8 commemorative German coins in case, 1968 (Object 5023, Box 1)
    w/ 2 business cards
  - paperweight w/coins, Bank of Adelaide, AUS Centenary anniv., 1965 (Object 5024, Box 1)
  - letter to Pres. Chun of Korea, thanking for Gwangwa Medal, 1982 July 21 (Object 5025, Box 2)
  - Alexandre Soljenitskyne bronze commemorative coin, 1970 (Object 5026, Box 1)
  - gold money clip from Colorado School of Mines centennial, 1974 February (Object 5027, Box 1)
  - silver spurs from Dr. E.C. Angeloz, Gov. of Cordoba, Argentina (Object 5028, Box 8)
  - photos from RF/L.A. Family Planning collaged on large board, 1969 March 10; Oversized (Object 5029)
  - oil painting of 3 women and baby, from RU (Object 5030)
  - certificate from City of Miami, 1987 July 22; DEFRAMED (Object 5031)
  - signed portrait, signature illegible, 1987 March 7 (Object 5033, Box 9)
  - gold key to city of Cleveland, 1975 March 1 (Object 5034, Box 1)
    w/ card of Mayor Ralph J. Perk
  - medal from Province of Tarlac, Phillipines, 1966 September 2 (Object 5035, Box 1)
  - 2 copies of citation for Province of Tarlac recognition, 1966 August 10 (Object 5036)
  - medal Grand Cross, Order of Boyaca, Columbia, 1972 November (Object 5037, Box 1)
  - 2 medals Order of Boyaca, w/ menu signed by "last 3 presidents of Columbia, S.A.", 1972 November (Object 5038, Box 6)
  - citation, Grand Cross, Order of Boyaca, Columbia, 1972 November; in brown tube (Object 5039, Box 9)
  - parchment of Hilal-I-Quaid-I-Azam award,from Pakistan, 1984 August 30; w/ letters in silver tube, in green box (Object 5040, Box 6)
  - 2 medals, Order of Manuel Amador Guerrero, Panama (Object 5041, Box 6)
  - Grand Officer, Order of Manuel Amador Guerrero, Panama, 1974 March 11 (Object 5042)
  - silver $5 coin from Ethiopia, set in plastic case, 1972 (Object 5043, Box 1)
  - 2 coins of Simon Bolivar and Antonion Jose de Sucre, 1980; set in red velvet box (Object 5044, Box 1)
  - Commander, National Order of the Lion, Senegal, 1973 October 10 (Object 5045)
  - Grand Officer of National Order, from pres. of Ivory Coast, 1915 May 12; in tube w/ 2 notes (Object 5046, Box 9)
  - German Knight Commander's Cross of the Order of Merit, 1977 October 20 (Object 5047, Box 2)
    w/ unsigned letter
  - photo w/ newspaper clipping, DR w/ Pres. Sandro Pertini, Italy, 1982 April 1 (Object 5048)
  - American Horticultural Society Award, 1987 May 15 (Object 5049)
    accepted by Peggy Rockefeller, w/ note
  - signed photo from "Republican Inner Circle" (Object 5050)
  - signed photo of DR w/ 2 men, 1972 July (Object 5051)
  - membership certificate, The Presidential Trust, w/ letter, 1980 (Object 5052)
    Republican fundraisers
  - cartoon of businessmen, orig. New Yorker Magazine, "Miss Victor" written on back (Object 5053)
  - Alexis de Tocqueville Society Award/United Way of America, 1987 April 27; see # 4038 (Object 5054)
  - plaque, Real Estate Deal of the Year for Embarcadero Center, 1998 (Object 5055)
  - Advertising Council Annual Public Service Award album, 1971 December 13 (Object 5056, Box 9)
  - Honorable mention Banker of the Year-silver Tiffany bowl, 1981 (Object 5057, Box 1)
  - Preservation League of NYS Pillar of NY Award, 1995; cut crystal in black clamshell (Object 5058, Box 8)
  - unsigned charcoal sketch "Rockefeller JR", 1962 May 1 (Object 5059)
  - Univ. Of Liberia Honorary Doctorate, w/ invite, program, etc, 1979 February 13; documents separated (Object 5060, Box 9)
  - Univ. Of Liberia Honorary Doctorate - documents, 1979 February 13; Documents (Object 5060, Box 2)
  - large metal & plastic medallion, from Governor of NW Frontier Providence in Pakistan, in green velvet box (Object 5061, Box 4)
  - plaque from King of Thailand, for Suan Luang Rama Park, 1988 July 21; in large purple velvet box, w/ note (Object 5063, Box 11)
  - silver tray from Dr. T.S. Lin, Chinese Natll Fed. Of Industries, 1981 October 10; in red patterned box, w/ letter (Object 5064, Box 4)
  - paperweight: bust of Albert Schweitzer, 1971 (Object 5065, Box 1)
  - gold coin from Bank of Iran-10 Years of Service, 1969 (Object 5066, Box 1)
  - gold coin, House of Representatives, Indonesia, 1988 September (Object 5067, Box 1)
  - silver bowl, engraved "Mr. & Mrs. Gamal A. el Sadat" (Object 5068, Box 1)
  - 22 ct. gold coin, made in Austria in honor of moonlanding, 1970 December 21 (Object 5069, Box 1)
  - Gold coin, engraved with ant, "Bene de re nostra Meritis Labore" (Object 5070, Box 1)
    ("benefit from our hard work"?)
  - small plaque from Bank of Ireland, w/ note, 1974 December 26 (Object 5071, Box 1)
  - bronze seal of the President (Reagan) (Object 5072, Box 1)
  - silver coin from Central Bank of Nicaragua, 1964 (Object 5073)
  - bolt from construction of Chase Manhattan Bank Building, 1959 September 9 (Object 5074, Box 8)
  - 18k gold pin "Pebble Beach, Crosby, Pro Am California" (Object 5075, Box 1)
  - mini silver shovel, General Grant Houses groundbreaking, 1954 July 14 (Object 5076, Box 8)
    from Morningside Heights Inc
  - trowel, from laying cornerstone of Interchurch Center, 1958 October 12 (Object 5077, Box 8)
  - Commander, Legion of Honor, France, 1974 December 27; in airmail tube (Object 5078, Box 9)
  - black baton, Harvard Alumni Assoc., 1961 June 15 (Object 5079, Box 8)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Rockefeller University, w/ program, 1980 June 11; in gray tube (Object 5080, Box 2)
  - membership card, Albert Gallatin Association (Object 5081, Box 1)
  - money clip, World's Fair 1964 in New York (Object 5082, Box 1)
  - brass elephant tie pin "Republican" (Object 5083, Box 1)
  - silver Mexican money clip (Object 5084, Box 1)
  - paperweight, Governer's Club (Object 5085, Box 1)
  - tie clip, from Exec. Committee, American Bankers Assoc., 1972 (?); w/ note (Object 5086, Box 1)
  - silver tray from Chamber of Commerce, Mexico City, 1963 (Object 5087, Box 6)
  - signed photo of Pres. Kenan Euren of Turkey, 1988 July 1; in red velvet box (Object 5088, Box 6)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Univ. of Americas in Puebla, Mexico, 1988 September 20 (Object 5089, Box 5)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Polytechnic Institute of New York, 1977 June 3 (Object 5090, Box 5)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Middlebury College, 1974 October 3; w/ note (Object 5091, Box 5)
  - copy of news clipping on SR, from Christian Herald, w/letter, 1983 (Object 5092, Box 2)
  - Honorary Membership, Colorado School of Mines Alumni, 1974 May 9; w/ note (Object 5093, Box 2)
  - DR w/ man, signed by "Jimmy" (Object 5094, Box 2)
  - decree w/ 3 photos, membership in French region Medoc, 1953 May 23 (Object 5095)
  - high school diploma, Lincoln School of Teacher's College, NYC, 1932 May 27 (Object 5096, Box 2)
  - copy of front page, Humboldt Standard, CA w/ photo, 1926 July 6 (Object 5097, Box 2)
  - Citation, Colorado School of Mines, 1974 (Object 5098, Box 1)
  - silver tray, NY Chamber of Commerce, 1958 September 6 (Object 5099, Box 1)
  - Honorary doctorate, Pace College, w/ writ, medals, 1970 November 5; speech stored seperately (Object 5100, Box 1)
  - Honorary doctorate, Pace College, speech, 1970 November 5; speech (Object 5100, Box 5)
  - photo album from trip to Dakar, Senegal, 1982 February (Object 5101, Box 9)
  - Charter Award from Council of Regents, St. Francis College, 1985 May 28 (Object 5102, Box 9)
  - cartoon of DR on top of the world, by Eugene Payne, 1976 (Object 5103, Box 3)
  - proclamation from Miami for Miami Friends of Caribbean/ Central American Action Day, 1987 July 22 (Object 5104, Box 3)
  - charcoal cartoon by Warren King, 1973 May 23 (Object 5105, Box 3)
  - front page & picture from China Daily, 1988 May 25; Oversized (Object 5106, Box 3)
  - sale of Rock Center land to Rockefeller Group, from Columbia, 1985 February 28 (Object 5107)
    w/ letter from DR
  - poster "Views from Governor's Island" by Duchein, w/ letter, 1976 May (Object 5108)
  - small key of seal of City of Meridian, engraved to DR on back, 1913 January 6; in small plastic box (Object 5109, Box 1)
  - 2 Polish commemorative coins, 1976; in red box (Object 5110, Box 1)
  - Pan American Society Gold Medal on ribbon, with pin & note, 1977 September 29 (Object 5111, Box 1)
  - gold apple pin, given by J. Javitz (Object 5112, Box 1)
    Acc. 1977 August 2
  - conferral of Knight Grand Commander, from Pres. of Liberia, 1979 February 13; several green typed sheets (Object 5113, Box 2)
  - 2 medals from Liberia,poss. Knight Grand Commander awards (Object 5114, Box 1)
  - tie patterened w/ seal of University of Chicago, given by their Board of Trustees, chairman Robert W. Reneker (Object 5115, Box 1)
  - photo w/ letter from groundbreaking at Interstate North, GA, 1979; DEFRAMED (Object 5116, Box 2)
  - commemorative plate, tribute to Gerald R. Ford, 1977 October 26; w/note stored seperately (Object 5117, Box 1)
  - commemorative plate, tribute to Gerald R. Ford - note, 1977 October 26; with Plate stored separately. (Object 5117, Box 8)
  - small keychain w/ honorary membership to Beta Gamma Sigma, NY University, 1980 December 8; diploma stored seperately (Object 5118, Box 1)
  - small keychain w/ honorary membership to Beta Gamma Sigma, NY University - diploma, 1980 December 8; Diploma. Associated material stored separately. (Object 5118, Box 5)
  - paperweight, Intll Executive Service Corps 15th anniversary, 1979 (Object 5119, Box 1)
  - Christian A. Herter Award, from World Affairs Council, bronze medal, w/ documents stored seperately (Object 5120, Box 1)
  - Christian A. Herter Award, from World Affairs Council, Documents. Medal and associated material stored separately. (Object 5120, Box 2)
  - paperweight, CEO of the Year Award, from Financial World, 1980; in red velvet bag (Object 5121, Box 1)
  - paperweight, CEO of the Year Award, from Financial World - associated materials., Associated materials. (Object 5121, Box 2)
  - Berent Friele Service Medal, for Latin America work, 1980 December 16 (Object 5122, Box 1)
  - mounted medal from Univ. of Riyadh, Saudi Arabia, w/ letter (Object 5123, Box 6)
  - appt to President's Council, American Inst. Of Management, DEFRAMED (Object 5124, Box 2)
  - bronze statue "El Gauchito Desafiante" by Zorrilla San Martin, given by Pres. Miguel P. Vilaro of Uruguay, 1986; w/ correspondence stored separately (Object 5125, Box 7)
  - bronze statue "El Gauchito Desafiante" by Zorrilla San Martin, given by Pres. Miguel P. Vilaro of Uruguay - associated correspondence, Correspondence - Statue stored separately. (Object 5125, Box 2)
  - Community Council of Greater New York plaque, 1986 June 19 (Object 5126, Box 9)
  - tribute, signed w/ picture of crystal bird, from Above & Beyond Club in Chase Manhattan folder, 1980 December 23 (Object 5127, Box 5)
  - signed card w/ photo for retirement, Chase Manhattan Bank, 1981 April 21; Some materials stored separately. (Object 5128, Box 5)
  - signed card w/ photo for retirement, Chase Manhattan Bank, 1981 April 21; some materials stored separately. (Object 5128, Box 3)
  - inscribed portrait of Asian man, identity unknown, arr. 1981 December (Object 5129)
  - photo of DR w/ Taiwan's Minister of Finance K. T. Lee and Frank Stankard, with caption, 1974 May 20 (Object 5130, Box 9)
  - Chase Award for 90th Birthday ("Icon"), 195 June 12 (Object 5131, Box 3)
  - Order of Guerrero, Republic of Panama, 1974 (Object 5132)
  - laminate poster on wood "Summer Jobs '84", 1984 March 8 (Object 5133)
  - gold & black gong from Tira Smithichote, Bangkok, Thailand to Rockefeller family, w/ response by DR, 1987 January 23; note is copy, in box w/ item (Object 5134, Box 10)
  - letter from Nixon on Ad Council Public Service Award, 1971 December 2 (Object 5135)
  - Capt Robert Dollar Award, Natll Foreign Trade Council, 1964 (Object 5136)
  - NY Urban Coalition Achievement Award, 1983 December 6 (Object 5137)
- Rockefeller University, 7
  - party for Mrs. Norton Zinder (Marilyn) at RU Faculty Club, Oversized (Object 6000)
    File Plan
    Graphic Services - Photographs. Former Classification: I 529.
  - Raynard F. Biemiller retirement party at RU Faculty Club, 1975 September 24; Oversized (Object 6001)
  - 20 Anniversary of Faculty Club, retirement of Frederick Seitz, 1978 May 12; Oversized (Object 6002)
  - History of Biochemistry & Physiology, Joseph Needham, 1924; fragile scroll (Object 6003)
  - collage of pics of students and faculty (Object 6004)
  - winter at RU w/ Caspary Auditorium in background (Object 6005)
  - B&W portrait of Darwin (Object 6006)
  - 4 drawings by Louis Schmidt (Object 6007)
    given by Ruth Mandelbaum, 1986 July
  - Black & white portrait of Einstein (Object 6008)
  - 2 graphs on causes of death, 1940; rolled together (Object 6009)
  - portrait of unidentified man, seated (Object 6010)
  - print of unidentified bust (Object 6011)
  - signed portrait of unidentified man (Object 6012)
  - signed portrait of unidentified man (Object 6013)
  - portrait of unidentified man (Object 6014)
  - large notebook of patients' information, 1921-1928 (Object 6015)
  - XIII Intll Physiological Congress in Boston (Detlev W. Bronk), 1929 August (Object 6016)
    D.W. Bronk papers. Former Classification: I 303-U.
  - Centennial Convocation of National Academy of Sciences, 1963 October 22; damaged (Object 6017)
  - "Homewood" at Johns Hopkins U (Detlev W. Bronk) (Object 6018)
    painted by H. Figura
  - 2 copies of summer semester transcripts (Karl Landsteiner), 1892; marked pkg # 15 (Object 6019)
    Karl Landsteiner papers. Former Classification: I 450 L239.
  - large bronze plaque engraved to Jacques Loeb (Object 6020)
    Jacques Loeb papers. Former Classification: I 450 L823.
  - small and large prints of Jacques Loeb portrait (Object 6021)
  - Stanford Moore academic cap, in hat box (Object 6022)
    Stanford Moore papers, Rockefeller University faculty.
  - silk green top hat, in hat box (Paul Weiss) (Object 6023)
    Paul Weiss papers. Former Classification: 450 W436.
  - characture of H.D.Dakin on wood, by Margaret Burns, 1914 (Object 6024)
  - portrait of Max Bergmann, member 1937-44 (Object 6025)
  - portrait of Leslie Tillotson Webster, member 1934-1943 (Object 6026)
  - portrait of Charles Lee Hoagland, member 1945-1946 (Object 6027)
  - portrait of Leonor Michaelis, member 1929-1940 (Object 6028)
  - portrait of Alexis Carrelmember 1912-1939 (Object 6029)
  - portrait of Wade Hampton Brown, member 1922-1942 (Object 6030)
  - portrait of Leslie Tillotson, member 1934-1943 (Object 6031)
  - portrait of Alexis Carrel, member 1912-1939 (Object 6032)
  - portrait of Karl Landsteiner, member 1922-1939 (Object 6033)
  - portrait of Wade Hampton Brown, member 1922-1942 (Object 6034)
  - etching of A. von Humboldt, poor condition (Object 6035)
  - portrait of Karl Landsteiner, member 1922-1939 (Object 6036)
  - portrait of James Bumgardner Murphy, member 1922-39 (Object 6037)
  - portrait of Verlag von A. Hirschwald, Damaged (Object 6038)
  - framed letter from Theobald Smith to Dr. Krumbhaar, 1933 October 11 (Object 6039)
  - C. Ten Broeck Collection portrait of Simon Flexner (Object 6040)
    gift of R.M. Herriot 1986
  - C. Ten Broeck Collection portrait of Simon Flexner (Object 6041)
  - Flexner, Holt, Prudden, Welch, Herter, Smith, Biggs, seated (Object 6042)
    w/ torn note
  - portrait of Rufus Cole, received 3/18/86 (Object 6043)
  - print of "Jenner" (Object 6044)
  - portrait of William H. Welch (Object 6045)
  - small B&W print of Grand Canyon (Object 6046)
  - John A. Abel portrait, signed to Michaelis (Object 6047)
  - portrait of JDR SR (Object 6048)
  - print portrait of John Abernathy, by Sir John Thomas Pinx (Object 6049)
  - 2 copies of portrait of Frederick T. Gates, 1 signed (Object 6050)
  - Dept of Experimental Biology Laboratory at Wood's Hole (Object 6051)
  - small portrait of Simon Flexner, 1927 (Object 6052)
  - portrait of William H. Welch in office (Object 6053)
  - portrait of Rudolph Virchow (Object 6054)
  - portrait of Alexis Carrel (Object 6055)
  - portrait of Emil Adolf von Behring (Object 6056)
  - large B&W portrait of Samuel Meltzer (Object 6057)
  - 10 charts on mortality rates, from "The Burden of Diseases in the US" by Alfred Cohn and Claire Lingg, 1950; see #6063 (Object 6058)
  - Alfred Cohn: resolution of 48th Congress on death of Edward A. Lasker, rolled w/ # 6060-6062 (Object 6059)
  - Alfred Cohn: painting of bamboo by Hsia Chang, rolled w/ # 6059, 6061, 6062 (Object 6060)
  - Alfred Cohn: drawing "Wanderings of Odysseus", rolled w/ #6059, 6060, 6062 (Object 6061)
  - Alfred Cohn: certificate for 25 years w/ NY Federation and Jewish Philanthropic Society, rolled w/ #6059-6061 (Object 6062)
  - mock-up edition of "Burden of Diseases in the US", Alfred Cohn, see #6058 (Object 6063)
  - "Development of Cardiac Surgery 1896-1991", Yale Univ Press, 1992 April 1; bound in large album (Object 6064)
  - collage of articles about Sydenham Institution (Object 6065)
- Harold P. Fabian, 8
  - metal stirrup from Harold P. Fabian papers (Object 7001, Box 1)
  - metal seal with fixed handle, "Fed J. Fabian Co 1910, Salt Lake City, Utah (Object 7002, Box 1)
  - bronze statue of a road runner, undated (Object 7003, Box 1)
  - small gold plate from the California & Hawaii Sugar Refining Co 25th Anniversary, 1931 March 10 (Object 7004, Box 1)
    given to Harold Fabian's son, Ferdinand J. Fabian
  - Nathan Hale Alumni Award, from Yale, 2007; small ceramic dish (Object 7005, Box 1)
  - small B&W picture in bronze frame w/glass: Minnie R. Fabian (mother of Harold) (Object 7006, Box 1)
- Rockefeller Foundation Decorations, 9
  - D61b: Scroll, parchment, 1956 July 26; 12.5 x 17; Crinkled (Object 8000, Box 1)
    Citation
  - Lasker Group Award from American Public Health Assoc., given to IHD/RF, bronze winged victory on marble base, very heavy (Object 8001)